{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785799732","data":{"timestamp":" 946785799732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mla_mfu-mwa-mla"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mla"," userResponse":" mla"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785805433","data":{"timestamp":" 946785805433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ngo-mme-mba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785811066","data":{"timestamp":" 946785811066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nja-nye-nga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785815855","data":{"timestamp":" 946785815855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nya_shu-nya-mki"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785820475","data":{"timestamp":" 946785820475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyu_nje-nyu-bwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyu"," userResponse":" nyu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785825537","data":{"timestamp":" 946785825537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ngi-bwa-tha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785830379","data":{"timestamp":" 946785830379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sha_sha-tha-nde"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785835304","data":{"timestamp":" 946785835304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twi_twi-mza-twa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785840683","data":{"timestamp":" 946785840683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_sho-mko-mfa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785846453","data":{"timestamp":" 946785846453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdo"," userResponse":" mka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785853452","data":{"timestamp":" 946785853452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdo"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785859898","data":{"timestamp":" 946785859898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdo"," userResponse":" mdo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785865676","data":{"timestamp":" 946785865674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" aadd95c3-3e2d-4e3d-be38-500c8581cef7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mdo_mka-mdo-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785882246","data":{"timestamp":" 946785882246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nge_vya-nge-dha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nge"," userResponse":" nge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785887324","data":{"timestamp":" 946785887324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_mzi-nji-mre"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785892097","data":{"timestamp":" 946785892096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwi"," userResponse":" mwi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785897636","data":{"timestamp":" 946785897635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_ndo-nda-she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785902331","data":{"timestamp":" 946785902331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785907139","data":{"timestamp":" 946785907139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sho_mgu-sho-nji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785912004","data":{"timestamp":" 946785912004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twe_nja-dha-twe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twe"," userResponse":" twe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785916897","data":{"timestamp":" 946785916897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_kha-mna-bwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785921720","data":{"timestamp":" 946785921720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_bwa-mki-mpe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785926833","data":{"timestamp":" 946785926833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ndi-msa-bwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785932609","data":{"timestamp":" 946785932608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ndi-msa-bwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785967293","data":{"timestamp":" 946785967293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070301"," gameId":" c78b50a5-6cdc-4073-bc76-6093e22cd54b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ndi-msa-bwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}